Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: 17th of August, 2023. At ptgms.space, we take your privacy seriously and are committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, and safeguard your data when you access and use our website. Please read this policy carefully to understand our practices regarding your information.

1: Information We Collect:
--------------------------

We only collect anonymized IP addresses for the purpose of analyzing website traffic and ensuring the security of our website. We do not collect any personally identifiable information or store any cookies. All logs are automatically deleted after two weeks have passed.

2: Use of Collected Information:
--------------------------------

The anonymized IP addresses we collect are used solely for the purpose of analyzing website traffic patterns, detecting and preventing security threats, and improving the overall user experience. We do not use this information to identify or track individual users.

3: Data Sharing:
----------------

We do not sell, rent, or share any of the information collected from our website, including the anonymized IP addresses, with any third parties. We are committed to keeping your data confidential and will only disclose it if required by law or if we believe such action is necessary to protect our rights or the rights of others.

4: Cloudflare and Data Collection:
----------------------------------

To ensure the security and availability of our website, we use Cloudflare as a DDoS protection and content delivery network (CDN) provider. While using Cloudflare, certain data may be collected by Cloudflare for their own purposes. However, we have configured Cloudflare to disable any options that could potentially identify individual users or track personal information. See the Privacy Policy of [Cloudflare](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/) for more information.

5: Third-Party Links:
---------------------

Our website may contain links to third-party websites or services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third-party websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those websites before providing any personal information.

6: Request of deletion
----------------------

If you want all your data we may have deleted, send us an e-mail. We will work out the details and make sure there is no trace of you.

7: Changes to Privacy Policy:
-----------------------------

We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Changes will be notified about at least 3 months in advance.

9: Contact Information:
-----------------------

If you have any questions, concerns, or requests regarding this Privacy Policy or our data practices, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://ptgms.space/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date indicated above and supersedes any prior versions.

Old privacy policies:
